idolwhite.com 2014-12-25

# 

Terms and Conditions

This Agreement is between Company and you ("you" or "Customer") This Section sets forth the terms and conditions which apply to the use by you of the Company Sites (as defined below) and any other subscription product or service offered for sale by Company and/or its affiliates (collectively, "Company "). The right to use any product or service offered by Company is personal to you and is not transferable to any other person or entity. Company reserves the right to make changes to the Company sites, policies, and these Terms at any time without notice. 

**1\. Use of the Company Sites.  
**The Company Sites contain links to other Web sites, resources and advertisers. Company is not responsible for the availability of these external sites nor does it endorse or is it responsible for the contents, advertising, products or other materials made available on or through such external sites. Under no circumstances shall Company be held responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any loss or damage caused or alleged to have been caused to a user in connection with the use of or reliance on any content, goods or services available on such external site. You should direct any concerns to such external site's administrator or webmaster.

**2\. Disclaimer of Warranty; Limitation of Liability**  
Company neither endorses nor is responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any opinion, advice or statement on the Company sites, nor for any offensive, defamatory or obscene posting made by. Under no circumstances will Company be liable for any loss or damage caused by your reliance on information obtained through the content on the Company sites. It is your responsibility to evaluate the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any information, opinion, advice or other content available through the Company sites. Please seek the advice of professionals, as appropriate, regarding the evaluation of any specific information, opinion, advice or other content, including but not limited to financial, health, or lifestyle information, opinion, advice or other content.

**3\. Indemnification.**  
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Company, its affiliates and their respective directors, officers, employees and agents from and against all claims and expenses, including attorneys' fees, arising out of the use by you of the Company Sites, including claims by other users of your equipment, access, products or membership.

**4\. Shipping.**  
Our standard ground shipping takes from 5 to 10 business days within the continental United States. For international orders, we ship via Federal Express. Generally international shipments take 14-21 business days from day of shipment unless customs causes a delay for some reason.

If you have not received your order within 21 days from your purchase date, please click on the link below visit our online customer care section to request a reshipment of your order.

If you entered the wrong address on our order form and we are forced to reship your package, there will be an additional shipping and handling charge equal to your original order.

To check the status of your order, update your mailing address or request reshipment because you never received your product, [Click Here to Manage your Order](http://www.websupportcenter.com/)

**5\. Sales and Distribution.**  
Distributor will not sell any Idol White product on eBay, Amazon, any of their affiliate's websites or any other auction website or online marketplace. Prices do not include and are net of any foreign or domestic governmental taxes or charges of any kind that may be applicable to the sale, licensing, marketing or distribution of the products. Distributor understands and acknowledges that all sales are final and that they are not entitled to return any product for a refund. Idol White will not be responsible for any delays or lack of delivery due to customs clearance issues.

**6\. Cancellation Policy.**  
Once an order has been submitted your credit card will be charged. Our ordering process is streamlined so your order will immediately be sent to processing and then shipping. Due to the high volume of orders we receive we will be unable to cancel an order after submitted. Please order carefully.

**7\. 90 Day Return Policy:**   

We take great pride in the superior quality of our products and want you to be pleased with your purchase. We believe in offering the very best value, quality and selection to our customers. You may return any unused and unopened item purchased from us for any reason within Ninety (90) days of your purchase. If you purchased your merchandise through a "Buy Three, Get Three Free" or similar offer, all items must be returned in order to receive a refund. If you return a partial amount of merchandise, you will forfeit the free product and receive a refund on the discount price per item based on the total purchase.

Your complete satisfaction is our ultimate goal. You may return any item shipped by Company, keeping the following in mind:

  * You should return the item to us within 90 days of your purchase date.
  * We do not accept items back that have been opened or used. Opened Items are Non Refundable.
  * Shipping and Handling Fees are Non Refundable.
  * **There is a $10.00 restocking fee for returns.**

To request a refund you must obtain an RMA (Return Authorization). Requests must be made online and submitted with your order information and explanation of the why you wish to return the product. Please do not call for an RMA. If you return your product without a RMA number you will not be refunded. Shipping and handling charges are non-refundable. For returns via mail, you must carefully package the product, you are responsible for the cost of return shipping, and we must physically receive the return within the 90 day period. Company reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to reject any return that does not comply with these requirements. Once your return has been received, a credit to your card or refund check will be issued and an e-mail confirmation will be sent within 30 days.

*Refund Processing and Restocking Fee: $10 Per item e.g. 1 bottle return = $10 Fee. 2 bottle return - $20 Fee. 

**8\. Paid Offers:**   
On paid offers there is no continuity charges and you will only be billed once for your purchase. For example if you buy 1 bottle of dietrine you will be charged $39.95 plus shipping & handling. 

**9\. Unlimited Refill Program Terms: * NO Monthly Charges * NO Auto-Shipping **   

This offer will allow you to order the product every 30 days and pay only $16.97 shipping included on a monthly basis month after month via our automated [order management system](http://www.websupportcenter.com/) by request only. Once your original purchase supply has been depleted, you will be able to request additional supplies every thirty days. If you choose to return your original purchase for any reason, your enrollment to our membership program will be forfeited. Customers will be given a 3-month notice of product cancellation. Unlimited Supplies subject to availability.

**10\. Manufacturer Coupon Offer Terms:**   

Try product for 30 days. If you are not completely satisfied for any reason, you can return it for a refund. Starting 30 days from your order date, you can request a new 30-day supply for FREE every month and only pay $14.97 s/p. For coupon eligibility, simply collect four refills & complete coupon form at [http://www.websupportcenter.com](http://www.websupportcenter.com/downloads/coupon-form.pdf)

**11\. Collection Efforts:**

You understand that Discount Rewards is a monthly-billed continuity program, and a monthly payment obligation for you. Should Discount Rewards be unable to successfully process your payment for a given month of program benefit eligibility, you understand and acknowledge that, if your payment has not been processed for more than fifteen (15) days, Discount Rewards shall be entitled to seek collection of the unpaid funds using either internal or third party collection efforts. You understand and agree that, should Discount Rewards seek collection of unpaid funds as prescribed herein, that Discount Rewards shall be entitled to assess a twenty dollar ($20.00) penalty to re-coup the cost of collection efforts on your account. You further understand and agree that non-payment of a validated payment obligation may entitle Discount Rewards to report the matter to credit agencies, which may negatively impact your credit score.

**Legal Disclaimer  
**Statements made by Company have not been evaluated by the food and drug administration. The FDA Dose not evaluate or test herbs. These products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any illness or disease. Consult with your physician for diagnosis or treatment. Use herbs as per instructions and always watch for any allergic reactions. 

The information presented on this site is not presented with the intention of diagnosing any disease or condition or prescribing any treatment. It is offered as information only, for use in the maintenance and promotion of good health in cooperation with a licensed medical practitioner. 

In the event that any individual should use the information presented on this website without a licensed medical practitioner's approval, that individual will be diagnosing for him or herself.

No responsibility is assumed by the author, publisher or distributors of this information should the information be used in place of a licensed medical practitioner's services. No guarantees of any kind are made for the performance or effectiveness of the preparations mentioned on this website. Furthermore, this information is based solely on the traditional and historic use of a given herb, or on clinical trials that are generally not recognized by any US government agency or medical organization. 

This information has not been evaluated by the US Food and Drug Administration, nor has it gone through the rigorous double-blind studies required before a particular product can be deemed truly beneficial or potentially dangerous and prescribed in the treatment of any condition or disease. 

Herbal Safety Guidelines

Before using an herb you are unfamiliar with, find out its medicinal properties. Research it thoroughly and/or consult with an appropriately qualified practitioner or expert. If you are taking prescription drugs, or have a medical condition check with an appropriately qualified practitioner before using herbs medicinally. Herbs have shown overwhelming evidence that they work. Just because a small amount works well does NOT mean that more is better. As individuals we all have different constitutions, sensitivities, allergic reactions and possible health conditions. The following are merely guidelines. They include herbs offered on our websites. This list does not help with administering information on possible interactions and contraindications with prescription medicine. This needs to be discussed with your physician.

**Should I check with my doctor or healthcare provider before using a supplement?**  
This is a good idea, especially for certain population groups. Dietary supplements may not be risk-free under certain circumstances. If you are pregnant, nursing a baby, or have a chronic medical condition, such as, diabetes, hypertension or heart disease, be sure to consult your doctor or pharmacist before purchasing or taking any supplement. While vitamin and mineral supplements are widely used and generally considered safe, you may wish to check with your doctor or pharmacist before taking these or any other dietary supplements. If you plan to use a dietary supplement in place of drugs or in combination with any drug, tell your health care provider first. Many supplements contain active ingredients that have strong biological effects and their safety is not always assured in all users. If you have certain health conditions and take these products, you may be placing yourself at risk.

**Some supplements may interact with prescription and over-the-counter medicines.**  
Taking a combination of supplements or using these products together with medications (whether prescription or OTC drugs) could under certain circumstances produce adverse effects. Be alert to advisories about these products, whether taken alone or in combination. For example: Coumadin (a prescription medicine), ginkgo biloba (an herbal supplement), aspirin (an OTC drug) and vitamin E (a vitamin supplement) can each thin the blood, and taking any of these products together can increase the potential for internal bleeding.

**Some supplements can have unwated effects during surgery.**  
It is important to fully inform your doctor about the vitamins, minerals, herbals or any other supplements you are taking, especially before elective surgery. You may be asked to stop taking these products at least 2-3 weeks ahead of the procedure to avoid potentially dangerous supplement/drug interactions -- such as changes in heart rate, blood pressure and increased bleeding - that could adversely affect the outcome of your surgery.

**Not to be used during pregnancy, or if you are nursing:**  
Alkanet, Aloe, Angelica, Anise, Anise Star, Arnica, Ashwaganda, Barley Grass, Barberry, Basil, Bitter Melon, Black Cohosh, Bladderwrack, Blessed Thistle, Blood Root, Blue Cohosh, Blue Flag, Blue Vervain, Borage, Buckthorn, California Poppy, Cascara Sagrada, Catnip, Celandine, Celery, Chervil, Cinnamon, Club Moss, Comfrey, Coltsfoot, Cubeb, Dong Quai, Elecampane, Ephedra, False Unicorn, Fenugreek, Feverfew, Ginger, Golden Seal, Gravel, Guarana, Gymnema, Horehound, Horsetail, Hyssop, Juniper, Lemongrass, Licorice, Lobelia, Lovage, Lungwort, Mace, Motherwort, Mugwort, Muira Puama, Myrrh, Neem, Oregon Grape, Osha, Parsley, Pennyroyal, Pleurisy, Prickly Ash, Red Clover, Rhodiola, Rosemary, Rue, Sage, Sassafras, Sarsaparilla, Senna, Shepherds Purse, Spikenard, Turkey Rhubarb, Turmeric, Uva Ursi, Vitex, Watercress, White Sage, Wormwood, Yarrow

**Not for persons with history of kidney stones, liver disorders, renal dysfunction or inflammation.**  
Cubeb, Essiac, Horsetail, Hydrangea, Juniper Berries, Kava Kava, Parsley Root, Pennyroyal, Sheep Sorrel, Shepherds Purse, Suma, Sumac, Uva Ursi, Yellowdock, Yohimbe

**Not recommended for person currently taking blood thinning medications:**  
Alfalfa, Angelica, Cramp Bark, Cubeb, Dong Quai, Ginkgo, Meadowsweet, Red Clover, Sarsaparilla, Yohimbe

**Not for persons with stomach inflammation/ulcers serious digestion and/or liver problems. May cause gastrointestinal upset:**  
Black Haw, Blue Flag, Chaparral, Club Moss, Crampbark, Devils Claw, Eucalyptus, Elecampane, Essiac, Gentian, Ginger, Licorice, Lobelia, Parsley Root, Pleurisy, Pygeum, Solomans Seal, Tribulus, Turmeric, Yohimbe

**Not for long-term use:**  
Bilberry Leaf, Black Walnut, Blessed thistle, Borage, Cascara Sagrada, Comfrey, Coltsfoot, Chaparral, Elecampane, Ephedra, Flax, Horsetail, Gentian, Goldenseal, Guarana, Juniper berries, Licorice, Lobelia, Lungwort, Mullein, Nettle Root, Rhubarb, Sage, Sassafras, Sarsaparilla, Senna, Sheep Sorrel, Wild Cherry, Wormwood, Uva Ursi, Yohimbe

**To be used only under the supervision of an expert qualified in the appropriate use of this substance:**  
Calamus, Horse Chestnut, Lobelia, Licorice, Mandrake, Poke, Tonka

Do not use if you have abdominal pain or diarrhea, discontinue if these occur. Consult health practitioner prior to use if pregnant, nursing, and taking medication or have a medical condition. Do not exceed recommended dose. Not for long term use:   
Aloe, Buckthorn, Cascara Sagrada, Senna, Turkey Rhubarb, Yohimbe

**May cause photo toxicity in some individuals at high dosage. Avoid long exposure to sun if using internally:**  
Angelica, Celery Seed, Orange Peel, Rue, St. Johns Wort

Seek advice from health practitioner prior to use if pregnant, nursing, have high blood pressure, heart or thyroid disease, diabetes, difficulty in urination due to prostate enlargement, or if taking mao inhibitor or other prescription drug. Reduce/discontinue use if nervousness, tremor, sleeplessness, loss of appetite or nausea occur. Do not exceed recommended dose. Keep out of reach of children:  
Ephedra, st. Johns wort, yohimbe

**Seek advice from a health practitioner before use if you have/may have had kidney or liver disease. Discontinue use if nausea, fever, fatigue or jaundice (dark urine, yellow discoloration of eyes) should occur:**

**Boldo, Chaparral**

Statements made by Company have not been evaluated by the food and drug administration. The FDA Does not evaluate or test herbs. These products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any illness or disease. Consult with your physician for diagnosis or treatment. Use herbs as per instructions and always watch for any allergic reactions. 

Privacy Policy

EFFECTIVE DATE: November 30, 2010

This Privacy Policy (Policy) discloses the practices of Company concerning personal information we obtain about you. By using Company, in any way accessing Company, or using other services of Company (collectively the Services), you are accepting the practices described in this Policy.

This Policy notifies you of: (a) what personal information of yours is collected when you access Company and/or use the Services or purchase any product; (b) how the information is collected; (c) how the information is used and shared; (d) our efforts to maintain the security of Sensitive Information; and (e) other details concerning your personal information and our policies.

This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Company does not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**  
Information collected by Company is stored in a single, secure database, accessible only by Company. Company collects information from our paying customers or other persons who use, attempt to use, or purchase Company products or the services at several different points and from different sources, all or some of which may apply to you.

*** Registration**  
When you sign up as a customer or potential customer, we ask for, and you are required to give, your name, address, zip code, telephone number, email address, credit card or checking account number, and credit card expiration date. Once you register as a customer with us, you are not anonymous to us.

*** Cookies**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computers hard drive through your Web browser.

*** Log Files**  
Company automatically receives and records information on its server logs from your Web browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. We use IP addresses and cookies to analyze trends, administer the site, track members and users movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to your personal information.

*** Information from Other Sources**  
for reasons such as improving personalization of our Service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.

**Use of Information**  
Information we collect is generally used for the following purposes:

1\. To build features that will make the services available on our site easier to use. This includes faster search requests, better member support and timely notice of new services and special offers.

2\. To improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our sites content, layout, and services. These uses improve our Services and better tailor them to meet your needs.

3\. To resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use. At times, we may look across multiple members or users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your information to identify members using multiple Member Ids or aliases.

4\. Sharing of Information. We may use the personal information that you supply to us and we will bring selected retail opportunities to you via direct mail, email, online and telemarketing. Company may sell or rent aggregated statistical information and user, member or former member specific information, including name, address, telephone number and payment information, to our marketing partners or other third-parties. If you want Company to stop sharing information it has about you in the future, you may notify us of this fact by contacting Company's Member Services department.

We reserve the right to disclose personal information, including Sensitive Information, when we believe that such disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law or a request by a government official, to protect the rights or property of Company, or to enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use. In the event that Company or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, member information and Sensitive Information may be some of the transferred assets.

**Use of Data Collected**  
We use your personal, demographic and profile data to enhance your experience at our site and to enable us to present content we think you might be interested in. We use your contact information to send you information about our company and promotional material from our partners. We may also use your personal, demographic and profile data to improve our site, for statistical analysis, for marketing and promotional purposes, send SMS alerts or notification, and for editorial or feedback purposes for our advertisers. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future telemarketing, SMS text-messaging, e-mails or postal mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of orders placed online. By using this site, you agree that you may be contacted in any manner contemplated in this section even if your number is found on a do not call registry, in-house list or similar registry.

**SMS Offering and Opt-out rights**  
By completing or submitting a registration form or partial registration form you are consenting to receive SMS, wireless or other mobile offering to your cell phone. You understand that your wireless carrier's standard charges and rates apply to these messages. For SMS text messages, you may remove your information by replying "STOP", "END", or "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received and we will remove your personal information within 10 days of receiving such request.

**Agents**  
We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from member lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing member services. They have access to personal and Sensitive Information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

**Special Offers and Announcements**  
Active customers and former customers will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter.

**Security**  
Company takes every precaution to protect our users and members Sensitive Information, both online and offline. Your Sensitive Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. Sensitive Information is encrypted and is protected online with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL.

Sensitive Information is also protected offline in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a billing clerk or member services representative) are granted access to Sensitive Information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security practices and changes in those practices. Finally, the servers that we store Sensitive Information on are kept in a secure environment. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to us using Company online contact form.

**Other Sites**  
Company forwards users and members to other sites. Please be aware that Company is not responsible for the business and privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware of this when you leave our site and to read the legal notices and privacy policies of each and every website you visit.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**  
If a members personal information changes we will endeavor to provide a way to correct or update that members personal data provided to us. Visit our [Customer Care](http://www.websupportcenter.com/) section to update

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our Policy, we will post these changes on our Homepage or provide other notification of our revised Policy so our users and members are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we disclose it.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection**  
Company serves general users of the World Wide Web. We support and comply with the Childrens Online Protection Act (COPPA) and we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13, nor do we share such information with third parties. Children under the age of 18 may use Company only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Special Notification for California Residents, Your California Privacy Rights**  
Individual customers who reside in California and have provided their personal information to Company may request information about our disclosures of certain categories of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to us using Company online contact form. Within thirty days of receiving such a request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this paragraph.
